Yes...
Evet...
we managed to sink one ship...
Gemilerden birini batırdım...
the one belonging to one Bon Kurei, a Baroque Works agent.
Baroque Works ajanı, Bon Clay'a ait olanı.
As for the other one...
Ama diğeri...
Hey, get a move on.
Hadi, kımılda.
So you let them get away...
Demek kaçtılar...
I can't believe I fell for that cheap trick...
Ucuz bir numaraya kandım.
They're good at running away.
Kaçmakta epey iyiler.
Miss Hina! Watch out!
Leydi Hina, dikkat edin!
It really pisses me off.
Cidden beni kızdırıyor.
Hina's going crazy!
Hina kızdı.
Why? Because of your incompetence?
Kendi beceriksizliğine mi kızdın?
No, that's not it.
Hayır, alakası yok.
Wowza! Miss Hina's Cage-Cage Fruit always gives me the tingles!
Vay be! Leydi Hina'nın Kafes-Kafes Meyvesi her seferinde içimi titretiyor!
"Everything that touches my body will be locked up."
"Bedenime dokunan her şey hapsolur."
Say it! Say your killer line! You gotta!
Söyle! Mottonu söyle! Lütfen söyle!
What the hell is this?! An iron lock...?!
Bu da ne böyle?! Demir pranga mı?!
You're what's driving me crazy, Smoker.
Beni kızdırıyorsun, Smoker-kun.
Haven't heard that one before...
Sanki daha önce duymadım!
Because...
Sana...
you almost seem happy...
Hasır Şapkalar'ın kaçtığını söylediğimde,
that Straw Hat got away.
bu, hoşuna gitti gibi.
Huh...?
Ha?
Me?
Öyle mi?
Why would I be?
Neden gitsin ki?
Who knows?
Bilmem.
And she spoke to me so formally, saying...
Ve sonra resmi bir dille bana dedi ki...
"I have something important to discuss, Dadd– No... Father."
"Size söyleyecek önemli bir şeyim var, Babacı– Hayır... Baba."
Even for a king like me, few things are harder to give up...
Kral bile olsam, benim için "babacım" unvanından vazgeçmek kadar zor olan...
than the title of "daddy."
çok az şey vardır.
What are you saying, Your Majesty?!
Ne diyorsunuz, Majesteleri?!
I still can't believe you're really gone...
Ölümünü kabullenemiyorum.
I can't even shed a tear...
Gözyaşı bile akıtamıyorum.
I wonder why... Pell...
Neden acaba? Pell.
Fire! Fire!
Ateş! Ateş!
What is it, Toto?
Ne oldu, Toto-san?
You've been laughing ever since the speech.
Konuşma bittiğinden beri gülüyorsun!
Good grief...
Cidden...
Did those sandstorms scramble your brain, old man?
O kum fırtınaları aklını mı aldı, ihtiyar?
It's a secret. I won't tell a soul.
Bu bir sır! Size söyleyemem!
Huh?
Ha?
What do you mean?
Bu da ne demek?
Take care, Luffy!
Kendine dikkat et, Luffy-kun!
Come back sometime and drink Yuba's water.
Bir gün Yuba'yı ziyarete gel ve tekrardan suyumuzdan iç!
– Huh?
– Ha?
Now, why are you guys just standing around?!
Neden öylece duruyorsunuz?
That well won't dig itself!
Gidip kuyu kazın!
Yeah, yeah...
Peki...
♪ So if the world ever changes ♪ ♪ I'll call out your name ♪
♪ Ama dünya bir gün değişse bile, çağırırım yine seni ♪
♪ We could return to a time ♪ ♪ when our lives were still the same ♪
♪ Döneriz belki o günlere, kaybetmediğimiz her anı gibi ♪
♪ Take me to the place ♪ ♪ where memories remain ♪
♪ Götür beni oraya, anıların solmadığı yere ♪
♪ Please don't ever let them fade ♪
♪ Lütfen unutulmasına asla izin verme ♪
As expected, Alubarna seems to be in bad shape.
Beklendiği gibi, Alubarna kötü durumda görünüyor.
Then let us make haste.
Öyleyse, oraya gitmeliyiz.
Yuba's restoration is also a priority,
Ama Yuba'yı ayağa kaldırmamız gerek.
since it's a crucial crossroad in the west.
Sonuçta orası batının merkezi.
Don't forget about fixing the Sandora River canals.
Sandora Nehri'nden gelen tüm kanallar da onarılmalı.
But what about the casino?
Peki kumarhane?
It's closing down.
Orası kapandı.
Let's go, everyone!
Gidelim, millet!
– Yeah!
– Tamam!
So why're we giving this guy special treatment?
O niye özel muamele görüyor?
No clue...
Bilmem...
But it was an order from Princess Vivi.
Ama Vivi-sama öyle söyledi. Yapacak bir şey yok.
It even wants to join the Supersonic Duck Squad.
Ayrıca Süpersonik Ördek Takımı'na katılacakmış.
But it's a camel...
Ama o bir deve.
Wow, you don't say?
Deme ya, gerçekten mi?
Well then...
Peki...
Thank you... for everything.
Her şey için... teşekkür ederim.
Seriously, you're so impatient.
Cidden sabırsız birisin.
I shouldn't let you go anywhere in that state.
Öyle yaralarla hareket bile etmemen gerekir.
I know. Farewell.
Biliyorum, görüşürüz.
Make sure to take it easy once you're home! Got it?
Şunu iyi anla. Eve gidince doğruca yatağa git!
Yeah, I've got it.
Evet, anlıyorum.
Oh... Hey, wait.
Ah sahi, dur biraz.
You forgot this. Here.
Bunu unuttun. İşte.
Now, Karoo!
Hadi, Karoo!
Let's go home... to Alubarna!
Eve, Alubarna'ya gidelim!
Captain Smoker...
Smoker-san?
Hey there, little lady.
Hey, küçük leydi.
How's the leg treating you?
Bacakların bugün nasıl?
P-Please stop talking like that.
L-Lütfen bana öyle demeyin.
Thank you, though...
Teşekkürler...
I saw their new bounties...
Yeni ödüllerini gördüm.
For them, these numbers are no surprise.
Rakamlar onlara uyuyor.
Do you know what his swordsman buddy did?
Arkadaşı kılıç ustası ne yaptı, biliyor musun?
You mean Roronoa?
Roronoa'yı mı diyorsun?
He slew 100 bounty hunters at Whisky Peak.
Whisky Peak'teki 100 ödül avcısını halletti...
In addition, he cut down Daz Bonez in Alubarna.
ve Alubarna'da Daz Bonez'u yendi.
Daz? The infamous assassin?!
Daz? Suikastçi olan mı?
He made a name for himself as a bounty hunter in the West Blue,
Bu, Batı Mavi'de ödül avcısıyken bildiğimiz ismi.
but in Baroque Works, he was known as Mr. 1.
Ama Baroque Works'ta Bay 1 olarak biliniyor.
Y'know, it's almost impressive how many big shots Crocodile brought to heel.
Crocodile'ın bu kadar ünlü ve güçlü karakteri yanına çekmesi etkileyici.
But even with all of them, he still lost.
Ama yine de hepsi kaybetti.
One of these days, we'll settle things with the Straw Hats.
Hasır Şapka Korsanları'yla başka bir zaman hesaplaşacağız.
Yes, sir!
Başüstüne!
Looks like we ditched the Marines.
Görünüşe göre Donanma'yı atlattık.
Hey, isn't that good news?
Onlardan kurtulduk, değil mi?!
Seriously...
Cidden...
what's with you sad sacks?!
Bu keyifsiz yanıtlar da neyin nesi?
– I miss her!
– Onu özlüyoruz!
Quit whining!
Sızlanmayı kesin!
If you wanted her to stay with us that badly...
Onu arkada bırakmak istemiyorduysanız,
you should've kidnapped her!
zorla alsaydınız!
You savage!
Seni kalpsiz!
You're the worst!
Adisin!
Moss Head.
Yosun Kafa.
Three-sword style...
Üç kılıç stili...
Hey, wait, Luffy.
Hey, bekle, Luffy.
"Three-sword style" isn't an insult.
"Üç kılıç stili" bir hakaret değil.
Four-sword style.
Dört kılıç stili...
The number isn't the issue...
Sorun sayı değil...
Listen, it's like calling natto smelly.
Dinle, natto'yu kullan. Natto: Mayalanmış soya fasulyesidir ve çok kötü kokar.
Of course fermented soybeans are gonna stink...
Natto gibi koktuğunu söyle.
Finally, we're out to sea.
Demek sonunda adadan kaçtık.
Yeah.
Evet.
Nice job.
Aferin.
You here for revenge?! Bring it!
İntikam mı arıyorsun?! Gel!
What is she doing here?
Sen niye buradasın?!
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
Düşman saldırısı! Düşman saldırısı!
Who is she?
O kim?
Who the hell cares?!
Kimin umurunda?
What an absolute knockout!
Ne kadar güzel bir kadın!
I thought I told you not to point dangerous objects at me.
Size tehlikeli şeyleri bana doğru tutmamanızı söylemiştim.
How long have you been on board?!
Ne zamandır bu gemideydin?
Oh, a while now.
Bir süredir.
These are your clothes, right? I'm borrowing them.
Bu elbiseler senin mi? Onları ödünç alıyorum.
What's your game, Baroque Works?!
Ne yaptığını sanıyorsun, Baroque Works?!
Monkey D. Luffy...
Monkey D. Luffy...
You haven't forgotten what you did to me, have you?
Bana ne yaptığını unutmadın, değil mi?
Luffy! What'd you do to that beautiful lady, you bastard?!
Luffy! Bu güzel bayana ne yaptın, lanet herif?!
Spit it out, you son of a bitch!
Derhal gemiden in.
Get off the ship immediately.
Konuş, seni pislik!
Hey, quit lying! I didn't do anything to you!
Hey, sen! Yalan söyleme! Hiçbir şey yapmadım!
Oh, but you did.
Evet, yaptın.
And it was absolutely unbearable.
Bana çok kötü bir muamelede bulundun.
So you need to take responsibility.
Sorumluluğu üstlen.
What's this "unbearable" thing you did, Luffy?!
O kim ve neler oluyor?
You'd better take responsibility or...!
Sorumluluğu üstlensen iyi olur, yoksa...!
I'm serious.
Çok ciddiyim.
Quit confusing me! What the heck do you want?!
Neden bahsettiğini bilmiyorum! Benden ne istiyorsun?!
I want... to join your crew.
Tayfana katılmama izin ver.
– Huh?!
– Ha?!
Administer that right away.
Bunu hemen ona içir.
It's the antidote for Crocodile's venom.
Crocodile'ın zehrinin panzehiri.
Even if he's buried in this rubble...
Burada gömülü kalsa bile,
he's made of rubber, so he might survive.
lastik vücudu hayatta kalmasını sağlayabilir.
Before, you told Crocodile...
O sırada...
that the only thing recorded here is history...
sadece tarihin yazılı olduğunu söylemiştin.
Why did you lie?
Niye yalan söyledin?
So you knew...?
Biliyor muydun...?
How cruel...
Çok kötüsün...
That stone tells nothing of this country's history.
Bu ülkenin tarihi o taşa yazılı değil.
It should only contain information regarding the weapon you seek.
Orada tüm yazılı olan, örgütünün istediği silahla ilgili detaylar.
And that includes its location.
Ve elbette silahın yeri.
If you had told Crocodile,
Crocodile için onu doğru çevirseydin,
this country would've fallen into his hands.
bu ülke şu anda onun olurdu.
Isn't that right?
Yanılıyor muyum?
It's of no concern to me...
İlgilenmiyorum...
Countries... People's lives... I honestly couldn't care less.
İnsanların ve ülkelerin yaşaması... Açıkçası hiç umurumda değil.
I never had any intention of handing that weapon to Crocodile.
Başından beri Crocodile'a silahı vermek niyetinde değildim.
I don't understand...
Anlamıyorum...
Then why did you come here?
Öyleyse buraya neden geldin?
I expected one thing, but hoped for another.
Umutlar ve beklentiler iki farklı şeydir.
What I was hoping to find... was the Rio Poneglyph.
Bulmak istediğim şey, Rio Poneglifi'dir. Rio Poneglifi: Gerçek Tarihi Metin.
Of all the poneglyphs scattered throughout the world,
Dünyadaki bütün poneglifler içerisinde,
it alone tells the true history.
gerçek tarihi anlatan sadece o.
That is the Rio Poneglyph.
O, Rio poneglifi.
What do you mean "true history"?
"Gerçek tarih" derken ne demek istiyorsun?
I don't care anymore...
Artık yeter.
I've searched for twenty years, exhausting every lead...
Yirmi yıl boyunca aradım ve bulduğum tek ipucu buydu.
This was my last hope... but it was just another dead end.
Bu yer benim son umudumdu ve başarısızlıkla sonuçlandı.
This is as fitting an end as any for someone like me...
Burada ölmem gerekiyorsa, bana uyar.
I'm so tired... I don't think I can live like this any longer.
O kadar yorgunum ki… Artık bu şekilde devam edemeyeceğim.
All I wanted was to know the history...
Tek istediğim tarihi öğrenmekti.
But too many enemies...
Ama hayalimin önünde...
stand in the way of my dream.
çok fazla düşman var.
Let me ask you a question...
Şunu merak ediyorum…
Can the untold history be brought to light?
Anlatılmayan tarih gün ışığına çıkarılabilir mi?
Are you saying that the poneglyphs hold that record?
Poneglifler'in o kaydı içerdiğini mi söylüyorsun?
Then why do we...
Öyleyse neden biz...
Alright, let's go.
Pekâlâ, gidelim.
Hold on!
Dur biraz!
I no longer have any reason to live!
Yaşamak için bir sebebim yok!
Just leave me here!
Beni burada bırak!
Why the heck should I listen to you?
Niye seni dinleyeyim ki?
You made me live when I wanted to die.
O sırada ölmeyi isterken, beni yaşamaya zorladın.
That's your crime.
Bu senin suçun.
I have nowhere to go and no home to return to.
Gidecek veya dönecek bir yerim yok.
So let me stay on this ship.
Bu yüzden bırak, bu gemide kalayım.
Oh, I see... Then I guess we have no choice. Welcome aboard.
Oh, anladım... O zaman başka seçeneğimiz yok. Hoş geldin.
– Luffy!
– Luffy!
Don't worry.
Endişelenmeyin.
She's not a bad person.
O kötü biri değil!
Mellorine! Mellor–
Mellorine! Mellor–
Pay attention!
Dikkatini ver!
Answer my questions honestly!
Sorularımı dürüstçe cevapla!
I'll ask you one more time.
Bir daha soracağım.
What's your name?!
Adın ne?!
Oh... I'm Usopp, by the way. Nice to meet you. Yep, nice to meet you.
Oh… Ben Usopp. Tanıştığımıza sevindim. Evet, sevindim.
My name is Nico Robin.
Nico Robin.
Okay, then, Nico Robin.
Tamam, Nico Robin!
What is your occupation?
Mesleğin nedir?
I'm an archaeologist.
Arkeologum.
An archaeologist?!
Arkeolog mu?!
I actually come from a long line of archaeologists.
Uzun bir arkeolog soyundan geliyorum.
The whole "wanted criminal" thing didn't happen until I was, oh... eight or so.
Aranan bir suçlu olma durumum, sanırım sekiz yaşlarımdayken başladı.
That was twenty years ago.
Bu, yirmi yıl önceydi.
Ever since, I've had to keep a low profile.
O zamandan beri dikkat çekmemeye çalışıyorum.
Since you were eight? You were alone that long?
Sekiz yaşından beri mi? Onca zamandır yalnız mıydın?
Well, no child could survive on the sea completely alone.
Hiçbir çocuk, denizde tek başına hayatta kalamaz.
For my own protection,
Kendimi korumak ve...
and to bring me closer to my goal,
hedefime ulaşmak için,
I've had to ally myself with various scoundrels and outlaws.
çeşitli haydutlarla ittifak yapmak zorunda kaldım.
That's the gist, anyway.
Hikaye bu.
As such, I've become quite adept at operating in the shadows.
Bu yüzden, gölgelerde çalışmada oldukça yetkin hâle geldim.
So I'm sure I can be of use to you all as well.
İşinize çok yararım.
Oh...? You sure are confident...
Oh...? Kendine çok güveniyor gibisin.
What's your specialty?
Uzmanlık alanın nedir?
Assassination.
Suikast.
Luffy! My investigation has concluded that she's way too dangerous!
Luffy! Onu sorgularken çok tehlikeli olduğu sonucuna vardım.
Are you guys listening?!
Dinlemiyor musunuz be?!
Seriously...!
Cidden...!
Being hoodwinked so easily... Pathetic!
Böylesine kolay aldatılmak… Zavallıca!
A few days ago, she was the VP of a crime syndicate.
Birkaç gün önce, bir suç örgütünün başkan yardımcısıydı.
As if we'd let someone like her join us!
Böyle birinin bize katılmasına nasıl izin verebiliriz?
You may have conned these morons, but I'm not so easy!
Bu aptalları kandırmış olabilirsin ama bende işe yaramaz!
Make one wrong move and you're out of here!
Bir şey yapmaya kalkışırsan, seni atarım.
Okay. I'll keep that in mind.
Peki. Bunu aklımda tutacağım.
Oh yeah, almost forgot...
Bu arada...
I brought some of Crocodile's jewelry with me...
Crocodile'ın mücevherlerinden birazını getirmiştim.
Wow, Big Sis! I love you!
Vay, Abla! Seni seviyorum!
– Hey, hey, hey, hey...
– Hey, hey, hey, hey...
Nami's been suckered.
Nami'yi de kaybettik!
That was a dirty trick.
Bu çok hilekârcaydı.
She's totally under her spell.
Tamamen büyüsüne kapılmış.
– Huh?
– Ha?
Oh, love...
Ah, aşk...
Floating love...
Yanında süzülen...
I'm driftwood that just lays its burnt body in that stream...
alev almış bir odun parçasından başka bir şey değilim.
Treasure...
Hazine...
I'm driftwood that has been struck by
Güzelliğin yıldırım gibi beni çarptı.
your thunderbolt of beauty and is caught in a raging torrent...
Irmakların paramparça ettiği odun parçasıyım.
A snack for you, my lady.
Sizin için, leydim.
Oh, thank you.
Oh, teşekkürler.
Welp, saw that one coming.
Hiç şaşırmadım.
Yeah...
Evet...
He never stood a chance, anyway...
Zaten hiç şansı yoktu...
In any case...
Ve böylece...
now that it's come to this, it's up to us to hold the line.
güçlü durmak bize kaldı.
Yeah, they're so naive! Buncha pushovers...
Evet, ne kadar zayıflar! Tamamen boyun eğdiler.
Hey, Usopp!
Hey, Usopp!
What?!
Ne?!
Chopper!
Chopper!
Should I call you "Robin my love"?
Sana Robin-chwan mı desem?
Or should it be "Robin my sweet"...?
Ya da Robin-swan mı?
Which should it be?
Hangisi?
Oh? Where're you going?
Oh? Nereye gidiyorsun?
What a woman...
Ne kadın ama...
Unlike Nami, she's got a certain mature allure about her...
Nami-san'dan çok farklı, daha olgun bir güzelliği var!
This ship is nice...
Güzel bir gemi...
Is it always this lively?
Her zaman böyle hareketli midir?
Yeah... It is.
Evet, öyledir.
I see.
Anlıyorum.
What the hell is her angle?
Ne dolaplar çeviriyor?
By the way, Miss Navigator... Is it smooth sailing right now?
Bu arada, Bayan Rotacı. Şu anda her şey yolunda mı?
Wind, weather... Both no problem!
Rüzgârda ve havada bir sorun yok!
It's going very smoothly, Big Sis!
Her şey mükemmel, Robin abla!
So she paid you off, huh?
Demek seni satın aldı, ha?
Sanji, is my snack ready yet?!
Sanji, atıştırmalığım hazır mı?!
Hold your horses!
Az sabırlı ol!